&gt；&gt；kyle simpson：我们所有的计划都准备好了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We have all our plan set up.
没有更多的声明代码，仍然有可执行代码。
There's no more declaration code, there is still executable code.
所以即使第一行看起来像一条语句，
So even though line one looks like one statement,
实际上是两个不同的东西。
it's actually two separate things.
这是var教师部分。
There's the var teacher part.
这就是编译器所处理的。
That's what the compiler handles.
然后是老师=“Kyle”部分，
And then there's the teacher = "Kyle" part,
这就是执行引擎要处理的。
that's what the execution engine's gonna handle.
现在，记得一点以前，
Now, remember a little bit ago,
我说过一个变量只能扮演两个角色。
I said that there's only two roles that a variable can play.
它可以是分配的目标，你可以在第一行看到，
It can either be the target of an assignment, and you can see on line one,
老师在那个角色中，它正在接受一个任务，它是目标。
the teacher is in that role, it is receiving an assignment, it's the target.
它可以发挥的唯一其他作用是在源位置。
The only other role that it can play is in the source position.
它会放弃它的价值。
It's going to give up its value.
您将从中检索值。
You're going to retrieve the value from it.
这就像我们在第十行看到的问题，就在那个位置。
That's like what we see on line ten, question, is in that position.
所以，这个老学派的术语是，这不是人们通常所说的，
So, old school terminology for this is, and this isn't what people normally,
如果你在维基百科上进行谷歌搜索，他们不会使用这些术语。
if you do a Google search on Wikipedia, they won't use these terms.
但我在二十多年前学的是计算机科学。
But I learned computer science more than two decades ago.
这是我以前学校的术语。
So here's my old school terminology.
我们过去把它称为左手边，LHS和RHS，右手边。
We used to refer to this as a left hand side, an LHS and a RHS, a right hand side.
就像在一个平等的左手和右手。
As in left and right hand of an equals.
现在，你可以称之为L值，R值。
Nowadays, you might call it an L value, an R value.
也许只是出于简单的目的，让我们称它们为源和目标。
Maybe just for simple purposes, let's call them source and target.
在一号线，老师在目标位置。
Here on line one, teacher's in a target position.
在第十行，问题，处于源位置。
On line ten, question, is in a source position.
你听懂了吗？
You follow that?
这是编译器拾取的一条信息。
That's a piece of information that the compiler picked up.
无论何时它创建了整个抽象树等等，它都知道每个
Whenever it created that whole abstract tree and all that, it knew that each
标识符，每个大理石，不仅是什么颜色，而且是什么位置。
identifier, each marble, not only what color it was, but what position it was in.
这很关键，我们稍后会看到为什么这是如此关键。
And that's critical, and we'll see in a bit why that's so critical.
重要的是要知道我们正在处理的东西正在接收一个值，
It's critical to know that we're dealing with something that's receiving a value,
它是一个目标，或者我们要找回它的价值，好吗？
it's a target, or we're gonna retrieve it's value, okay?
所以让我们按照JavaScript引擎的方式执行这段代码，
So let's then execute this code the way the JavaScript engine would,
所有的执行计划和范围都设置好了。
with all that execution plan and scope stuff set up.
每次我们进入一个范围，所有的bucket和
Each time we enter a scope, all of the plans for the buckets and
弹珠已经被创建了，所以现在我们已经准备好继续执行了。
the marbles will have been created, and so now we're ready to go ahead and execute.
我们又有两个人在说话了。
We have two people talking, again.
我们还有范围经理，因为他要分发弹珠。
We still have the scope manager, cuz he's gotta hand out the marbles.
但是我们现在也有一个不同的人在谈话。
But we also now have a different person talking in the conversation.
这就是虚拟机，它是执行代码的JavaScript引擎。
And that's the virtual machine, it's the JavaScript engine that's executing code.
所以一号线上的对话，记住，
So that conversation on line one, remember,
那里没有var，它会像这样。
there's no var there, it's gonna go like this.
我将扮演虚拟机或JavaScript引擎的一部分。
I'll play the part of the virtual machine or the JavaScript engine.
嘿，作用域管理器，JavaScript引擎在这里。
Hey, scope manager, JavaScript engine here.
我有一个名为Teacher的变量的目标引用。
I have a target reference for a variable called teacher.
你看，这是一个目标引用，它正在接受一个任务。
You see it's a target reference, it's receiving an assignment.
你听说过这个叫老师的大理石吗？
Have you ever heard of this marble called teacher?
我们在跟红桶说话，记得吗？
We're talking to the red bucket, remember.
它只能回答是或不是。
And it can only answer yes or no.
所以在这种情况下，它会回答什么？
So in this case, what's it gonna answer?
&gt；&gt；观众：是的。
&gt;&gt; Audience: Yes.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，怎么了？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, why?
因为在编译时我们正式声明了它，好吗？
Because at compile time we formally declared it, okay?
如果我们没有正式宣布，情况就不同了。
Had we not formally declared it, things are different.
但因为在编译时我们正式声明了一种叫做教师的东西，
But because at compile time we formally declared something called teacher,
现在我们知道了，是的，这是你的红色大理石。
now we know, yes, here's your red marble.
所以这基本上是一个查找。
So it's fundamentally a lookup.
我们在说，嘿，红桶，你有叫老师的大理石吗？
We're saying, hey, red bucket, do you have a marble called teacher?
如果是的话，请把它给我，好吗？
If so, please give it to me, okay?
这里是红色的大理石，这是你的大理石，好吗？
And here we get the red marble, here's your marble, okay?
那大理石怎么办？
And what are we gonna do with that marble?
我们要给它赋值。
Well, we're gonna assign a value to it.
大理石代表内存中需要分配的区域，
That marble represents an area in memory that needs to get assigned to,
本质上。
essentially.
因此，我们将从右侧获取值，在本例中为字符串
So, we're gonna take the value from the right hand side, in this case, the string
Kyle，并将其分配到红色大理石老师所代表的位置。
Kyle, and assign it to that location represented by the red marble teacher.
第三行到第六行，第八行到十一行，这些都是声明，
Line three through six, and line eight through eleven, those were declarations,
从某种意义上说，他们已经不在那里了。
they're not there anymore, in a sense.
他们已经被编译走了。
They've been compiled away.
因此，执行将移至第13行。
So, execution would move to line 13.
让我们讨论一下第13行是如何执行的。
Let's talk about how line 13 executes.
不要只跳过函数本身，它在内部是如何运行的。
Don't skip just to how the function itself, how it runs inside.
我们首先要问的是第13行本身是如何执行的。
We first have to ask how the line 13 itself executes.
因为JavaScript必须弄清楚并执行它。
Cuz JavaScript has gotta figure out that and execute it.
另一个类标识符也是如此，我们在函数中看到的东西
So is the other class identifier, the thing that we see there at the function
呼叫，它是在目标位置还是在源位置？
call, is it in a target position or is it in a source position?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：目标位置。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Target position.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：目标。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Target.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我听到一些目标，有人不同意吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I'm hearing some targets, anybody disagree with that?
&gt；&gt；扬声器5：第13行，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: Line 13, right?
&gt；&gt；观众：第13行。
&gt;&gt; Audience: Line 13.
other Class是在目标位置还是在源位置？
Is otherClass in a target position or in a source position?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：来源。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Source.
&gt；&gt；扬声器5：来源。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: Source.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，它在源位置。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, it's in a source position.
我们不会将某些内容分配给other Class。
We're not assigning something to otherClass.
所以，如果我们不分配给它，我们必须做什么？
So if we're not assigning to it, what must we be doing?
拉出一个值。
Pulling a value out.
我们想知道当前在标识符other Class中有什么。
We wanna know what is currently in the identifier otherClass.
因为，稍等片刻，我们就要把遗嘱执行者。
Because, in just a moment, we're about to turn the executor.
所以我们需要去拿它，那我们怎么办？
So we need to go get it, so what are we gonna do?
我们要做和以前一样的事情。
We're gonna do the same thing as before.
我们会说，嘿全球范围，嘿红色大理石，如果你愿意。
We're gonna say, hey global scope, hey red marble, if you will.
我有一个名为other Class的大理石的源引用。
I've got a source reference for a marble called otherClass.
你听说过那个大理石吗？
Have you ever heard of that marble?
答案是什么？
And what's the answer gonna be?
是的，这是件好事，因为我们需要一个大理石，如果我们要求的话，
Yes, that's a good thing, cuz we need a marble, if we're asking for it,
我们需要它。
we're gonna need it.
所以他给了我们大理石，我们怎么办？
So he gives us the marble, and what do we do?
我们从那个位置和记忆概念中提取值，
We pull the value out from that location and memory conceptual,
你把价值拉出来，这个时候的价值是什么？
you pull the value out, what is that value at this moment?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是other Class被声明指向的函数
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's the function that otherClass was declared to point
对吧？
at, right?
在编译时，other Class，
At compile time, otherClass,
标识符与该功能相关联。
the identifier, was associated with that function.
那个值在那里，或者对那个值的引用在那里。
That value is there, or that reference to that value is there.
这是一件好事，因为在第13行，我们看到的那些括号
So that's a good thing, because then, on line 13, those parentheses that we see
在第13行，他们执行我们刚刚从变量中取出的内容。
there on line 13, they execute the thing that we just pulled out of that variable.
如果我们从变量中取出一些不是函数的东西，比如，
If we pulled out of that variable something that wasn't a function, like,
空，或者未定义，您认为会发生什么？
null, or undefined, what do you think would happen?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：一切都会燃烧。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Everything would burn.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：[笑]一切都会燃烧。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: [LAUGH] Everything would burn.
这就对了。整个程序崩溃了
That's right. The whole program crashes down,
具体地说，会发生一个称为TypeError的错误，
specifically what would happen is an error called a TypeError,
因为我们会有一个类似NULL或undefined的值，
because we would have a value like null, or undefined,
但这不是一个可以作为函数合法执行的值。
but that is not a value that is legal to execute as a function.
所以我们用这种类型做了一些非法的事情，这就是所谓的TypeError，
So we're doing something illegal with that type, that's call the TypeError,
运行时错误，
a run time error,
我们正在做的事情的值是不允许用于该类型的。
where we're doing something with a value that's not allowed for that type.
谢天谢地，在这种情况下，我们有一个函数，所以我们可以执行它，
Thankfully, in this case, we got a function, so we can execute it,
这意味着行刑会移到哪一条线上？
which means execution moves to what line?
&gt；&gt；扬声器6：4。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Four.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第四行，第四行不再有var，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Line four, line four does not have a var on it anymore but
它确实有，什么样的行动？
it does have, what kind of operation?
&gt；&gt；扬声器6：有一个大理石。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Has a marble.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它有一个任务，所以
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It has an assignment, so
里面有什么对大理石的引用？
it's got what kind of reference to a marble in it?
&gt；&gt；扬声器6：接收者。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: A receiving one.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：目标。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Target.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：一个目标，确切地说，一个接收目标，一个目标。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A target, exactly, a receiving one, a target.
所以这段对话将一如既往地继续下去，就像在一号线上一样。
So that conversation is gonna continue exactly like it did on line one.
嘿，其他类的范围，嘿，蓝桶，
Hey, scope of otherClass, hey, blue bucket,
我有一个叫老师的大理石的参考资料，听说过吗？
I have a traget reference for a marble called teacher, ever heard of it?
答案是？
And the answer is?
&gt；&gt；观众：是的。
&gt;&gt; Audience: Yes.
凯尔·辛普森：这是你的大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your marble.
所以现在我们在内存中有了一个位置，
So now we have a location in memory,
那是和一号线不同的地方。
that's a different place than the one from line one.
它在内存中是一个不同的位置，因为它是一个不同的作用域。
It's a different location in memory, cuz it's a different scope.
我们有这个大理石，然后我们取Suzy的值，然后
We have this marble, and then we take the value Suzy, and
我们向它赋值，然后执行第四行。
we assign into it, then line four is executed.
到目前为止大家都还好吧？
Everybody good so far?
现在，五号线会发生什么？
Now, what's gonna happen with line five?
我们会掩盖一些细节，但是
We're gonna gloss over a bit of this detail, but
第五行是否有对标识符的引用？
Is there a reference to identifier on line five?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不是我们创建的，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Not one that we created, but
名单上有一个标识符，对吧？
there is an identifier on the list, right?
这里有一个概念意义上的大理石，叫做控制台，
There is a marble here in a conceptual sense, which is call console,
一定存在于某个地方。
that's got to exist somewhere.
JavaScript引擎为我们提供了类似于自动全局的功能。
The JavaScript engine has that available to us as sort of like an auto global.
不是我们创造的东西，但它仍然是可用的。
Not something we created, but it's available nonetheless.
所以同样的过程，看看发生了什么。
So the same process, look at what happened.
我们基本上会说，嘿，其他类的范围，
We would basically say, hey scope of otherClass,
你听说过一种叫做控制台的大理石吗？
have you ever heard of a marble called console?
因为那是在源位置。
Cuz that's in the source position.
现在，other Class曾经定义过一个名为console的大理石吗？
Now, has otherClass ever defined a marble called console?
那么接下来会发生什么，这是理解词汇范围的关键，
So what's going to happen then, and this is the key to understanding lexical scope,
如果我们找不到在作用域中引用的变量，
is that if we cannot find a variable that is referenced within the scope,
这是在范围内声明的，我们下一步做什么？
that was declared within the scope, what do we do next?
我们上升了一个层次，在这种情况下是全球范围，我们会说，嘿，
We go up one level, in this case to the global scope, and we would say, hey,
全局范围，您是否听说过称为控制台的标识符？
global scope, have you ever heard of an identifier called console?
尽管我们没有正式声明，但它是一个汽车全球，
And even though we didn't formally declare it, it's an auto global,
它已经在那里了，已经有一个叫做控制台的红色大理石了。
it's already there, there's already a red marble called console.
那么全球范围会做什么呢？
So what is global scope gonna do?
这是你的红色大理石，我们可以看看那个大理石。
Here's your red marble, and we can look on that marble.
它是一个对象，它记录了一个方法调用，等等
It's an object, it has a method call logged, and so on, and so
我们可以调用它。
we can invoke it.
一切都和我有关，好吗？
Everything with me on that, okay?
当在源位置引用变量时，
When you reference a variable in a source position,
你得先查一下，然后
you have to first look it up, and
当您在目标位置引用变量时，必须首先查找它。
when you reference a variable in a target position, you have to first look it up.
这就是这里的关键之处，就是其中涉及到一个查找过程。
That's the key takeaway here, is that there is a look up process involved.
到目前为止，我们的查找总是找到我们一直在寻找的东西。
So far our look ups have always found the thing that we were looking for.
一段时间后，我们将讨论当我们找不到它时会发生什么。
After a while, we'll talk about what happens when we don't find it.
但现在我们都在好的道路上。
But right now we're all in the good path.
我们正在寻找我们要寻找的一切
We're finding everything that we're looking for